[
    {
        "front": "いきます",
        "back": "To go",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "きます",
        "back": "to come",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "かえります",
        "back": "To return",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "みます",
        "back": "To see",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ききます",
        "back": "To hear",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "します",
        "back": "To do",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "たべます",
        "back": "To eat",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "のみます",
        "back": "To drink",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "よみます",
        "back": "To read",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほん",
        "back": "Japan",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんこく",
        "back": "Korea",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうごく",
        "back": "China",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "いんど",
        "back": "India",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "くに",
        "back": "Country",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "うち",
        "back": "Home",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "いえ",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "すき",
        "back": "Like         <adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "きらい",
        "back": "Dislike",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "おさけ",
        "back": "Wine, whisky, alcohol",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょくじ",
        "back": "Food (Meal)",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごはん",
        "back": "Food",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "すし",
        "back": "Raw fish rolled in rice",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "さかな",
        "back": "Fish",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "にく",
        "back": "Meat",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎゅうにく",
        "back": "Beef",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶたにく",
        "back": "Pork",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "とりにく",
        "back": "Chicken",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "とり",
        "back": "Chicken",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "たまご",
        "back": "Eggs",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎゅうにゅ",
        "back": "Milk",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "しごと",
        "back": "Work, job",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいが",
        "back": "Film, movie",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいがかん",
        "back": "Movie theater",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんがく",
        "back": "Music",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんぶん",
        "back": "Newspaper",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほん",
        "back": "Book",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "テレビ",
        "back": "TV",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "はなび",
        "back": "Fire crackers show",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "はなみ",
        "back": "Cherry flower",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "がっこう",
        "back": "School",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいしゃ",
        "back": "Company, office",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "おちゃ",
        "back": "Tea",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "みず",
        "back": "Water",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "これから",
        "back": "From now on",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "それから",
        "back": "After that",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ましょう",
        "back": "‘let’s’",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "と いっしょ に",
        "back": "‘with’",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんきょう",
        "back": "Study",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひるごはん",
        "back": "Lunch",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "あさ",
        "back": "Morning",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "けさ",
        "back": "Today Morning",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "よる",
        "back": "Night",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいしゅう",
        "back": "Next week",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいにち",
        "back": "Daily",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいばん",
        "back": "Every evening",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "さっか",
        "back": "Soccer",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "なら",
        "back": "(Place)",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "うりば",
        "back": "~department",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちか いっかい",
        "back": "First basement floor",
        "chapter": "N5 C6"
    }
]